When you compound for a month straight. This is
what those returns can look like.
Agriculture materials, again, those
natural resources, corn, sugar, just these
different natural resources that will
always be needed. It may not be right now,
but in the long term, the long horizon,
those who have access to these stocks and
shares will be the ones that will increase
their revenue. And just core funds. This
is the VOO, QQQ, the other again, trusted
ones for all this time. Those are some
good ones that you can get paid dividends
with monthly and just again, do that DCA
and into over time. And over time, you'll
see some nice gains. Or like I said, those
dividends that these ETFs and stocks
return. Again, my name is Nas. I am the
founder and the head person at INNERG
INTEL. Thank you again for watching this
video. If you have any questions after
watching this, if you want to get more
hands on training, I am running a
mentorship program. So if you want the
hands on, you know, talking, if you want
the hands on training, what I do to help
you reach out. It's open and available,
taking a limited people up until the end
of the year. So if that's you and you want
to talk to me more throughout the weeks,
throughout the months, I have that
available for you. Also, don't forget to
just do your own research. Everything that
I've said in this video is not financial
advice. I am not an expert. I am not a
financial advisor. I am simply just a
young brother who sees what is happening.
And I want to share with others what's
happening so that way they can start to
see, you know, plan for and understand
that there are opportunities out here for
us to get at and win, right? So thank you
again, Peace, carpe diem, and again,
remember to reprogram the mind, learn the
new systems and engage with the new ways
of this world. You don't want to be
behind, but you also, you know, don't want
to let it control you and take over what
you are already doing. All right, Peace.
I'll see y'all on the next frequency.